Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1948-1983, undated (bulk 1959-1979) MS 3009-RG 6.I MS 3009-RG 6TEST
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Editor-in-Chief: Subseries I.B. Henry Anatole Grunwald Files, 1944-1998 (bulk 1968-1987); 74.0 Linear feet; (74 boxes)
  - Subsubseries I.B.2. Interoffice Correspondence, 1972-1987; 20.0 Linear feet; (20 boxes)
    - 1980: Bear, Charles (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 14)
    - 1980: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 15)
    - 1980: Brown, Dale (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 16)
    - 1980: Dave, Ray (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 17-19)
    - 1980: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 20)
    - 1980: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 21)
    - 1980: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 22-24)
    - 1980: Heiskell, Andrew (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 25)
    - 1980: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 26)
    - 1980: Korn, Jerry (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 27)
    - 1980: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 28)
    - 1980: Lubar, Bob (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 29)
    - 1980: Manley, Joan (Offsite-box 1007, Folder 30)
    - 1980: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 1)
    - 1980: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 2)
    - 1980: Munro, J. Richard (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 3)
    - 1980: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 4)
    - 1980: Rogin, Gil [empty] (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 5)
    - 1980: Rosen, Clare Mead (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 6)
    - 1980: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 7)
    - 1980: Shepley, James (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 8)
    - 1980: Steed, Robert (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 9)
    - 1980: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 10)
    - 1980: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 11)
    - 1980: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 12)
    - 1980: Memos: A-Z (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 13-31)
    - 1980: Memos: A-Z [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1981: Bear, Charles (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 32)
    - 1981: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 33)
    - 1981: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 34-35)
    - 1981: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 36)
    - 1981: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1008, Folder 37)
    - 1981: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 1)
    - 1981: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 2-4)
    - 1981: Grum, Clifford (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 5)
    - 1981: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 6)
    - 1981: Jaroff, Leon (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 7)
    - 1981: Korn, Jerry (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 8)
    - 1981: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 9)
    - 1981: Loeb, Marshall (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 10)
    - 1981: Maness, Dave (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 11)
    - 1981: Manley, Joan (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 12)
    - 1981: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 13)
    - 1981: Munro, J. Richard (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 14)
    - 1981: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 15)
    - 1981: Rosen, Clare Mead (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 16)
    - 1981: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 17-18)
    - 1981: Steed, Robert (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 19)
    - 1981: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 20-21)
    - 1981: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 22)
    - 1981: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 23)
    - 1981: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 24)
    - 1981: Memos to all Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 25)
    - 1981: Memos: A-R (Offsite-box 1009, Folder 26-37)
    - 1981: Memos: S-W (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 1-3)
    - 1982: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 4)
    - 1982: Bear, Charles (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 5)
    - 1982: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 6)
    - 1982: Burgheim, Dick (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 7)
    - 1982: Constable, George (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 8)
    - 1982: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 9-10)
    - 1982: Crutcher, Larry (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 11)
    - 1982: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 12)
    - 1982: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 13)
    - 1982: Gart, Murray (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 14)
    - 1982: Gart, Murray [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1982: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 15-16)
    - 1982: Grum, Clifford (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 17)
    - 1982: Howell, Barbara (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 18)
    - 1982: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 19)
    - 1982: Jaroff, Leon (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 20)
    - 1982: Kerr, Jeanne: Time Inc. Donations (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 21)
    - 1982: Korn, Jerry (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 22)
    - 1982: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 23)
    - 1982: Loeb, Marshall (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 24)
    - 1982: Maness, Dave (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 25-26)
    - 1982: Manley, Joan (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 27)
    - 1982: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 28)
    - 1982: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 29)
    - 1982: Munro, J. Richard (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 30)
    - 1982: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 31)
    - 1982: Rogin, Gil [empty] (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 32)
    - 1982: Rosen, Clare Mead (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 33)
    - 1982: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 34)
    - 1982: Rukeyser, Bill [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1982: Ryan, Patricia (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 35)
    - 1982: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1010, Folder 36)
    - 1982: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 1)
    - 1982: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 2)
    - 1982: Memos: A-Z (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 3-20)
    - 1982: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 21)
    - 1982: Memos to all Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 22)
    - 1983: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 23)
    - 1983: Bear, Charles (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 24)
    - 1983: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 25)
    - 1983: Burgheim, Dick (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 26)
    - 1983: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 27-30)
    - 1983: Constable, George (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 31)
    - 1983: Crutcher, Larry (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 32)
    - 1983: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 33)
    - 1983: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 34)
    - 1983: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1011, Folder 35-37)
    - 1983: Graves, Ralph [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1983: Grum, Clifford (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 1)
    - 1983: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 2)
    - 1983: Jaroff, Leon (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 3)
    - 1983: Kerr, Jeanne (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 4)
    - 1983: Loeb, Marshall (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 5)
    - 1983: Maness, Dave (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 6-7)
    - 1983: Manley, Joan (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 8)
    - 1983: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 9)
    - 1983: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 10)
    - 1983: Munro, J. Richard (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 11)
    - 1983: Nicholas, Nicholas J. (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 12)
    - 1983: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 13)
    - 1983: Rogin, Gil (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 14)
    - 1983: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 15-17)
    - 1983: Ryan, Patricia (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 18)
    - 1983: Steed, Robert (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 19)
    - 1983: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 20)
    - 1983: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 21)
    - 1983: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 22)
    - 1983: Memos to Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 23)
    - 1983: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 24)
    - 1983: Memos: A-M (Offsite-box 1012, Folder 25-34)
    - 1983: Memos: N-Z (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 1-4)
    - 1984: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 5)
    - 1984: Bear, Charles (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 6)
    - 1984: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 7)
    - 1984: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 8-11)
    - 1984: Constable, George (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 12)
    - 1984: Constable, George [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1984: Crutcher, Larry (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 13)
    - 1984: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 14)
    - 1984: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 15)
    - 1984: Fahey, John: Operating Review (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 16)
    - 1984: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 17)
    - 1984: Hiland, R. Bruce (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 18)
    - 1984: Jaroff, Leon (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 19)
    - 1984: Kerr, Jeanne (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 20)
    - 1984: Kriss, Ron (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 21)
    - 1984: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 22)
    - 1984: Kunhardt, Phil [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1984: Lalli, Frank (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 23)
    - 1984: Loeb, Marshall (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 24)
    - 1984: Maness, Dave (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 25)
    - 1984: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 26)
    - 1984: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 27)
    - 1984: Munro, J. Richard (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 28)
    - 1984: Nicholas, Nicholas J. (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 29)
    - 1984: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 30)
    - 1984: Rogin, Gil (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 31)
    - 1984: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1013, Folder 32)
    - 1984: Ryan, Patricia (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 1)
    - 1984: Sheppe, P. Peter (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 2)
    - 1984: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 3)
    - 1984: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 4)
    - 1984: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 5)
    - 1984: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 6)
    - 1984: Memos to Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 7)
    - 1984: Memos: B-Z (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 8-17)
      "Memos: A" is not present.
    - 1985: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 18)
    - 1985: Barnet, Bruce (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 19)
    - 1985: Bingle, John (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 20)
    - 1985: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 21)
    - 1985: Constable, George (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 22)
    - 1985: Cox, Tony (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 23)
    - 1985: Crutcher, Larry (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 24)
    - 1985: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 25)
    - 1985: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 26)
    - 1985: Fahey, John [empty] (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 27)
    - 1985: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 28)
    - 1985: Grunwald, Mandy (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 29)
    - 1985: Hiland, R. Bruce (Offsite-box 1014, Folder 30)
    - 1985: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 1)
    - 1985: Kerr, Jeanne (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 2)
    - 1985: Kriss, Ron (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 3)
    - 1985: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 4)
    - 1985: Laffan, Doris: Stock Options (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 5)
    - 1985: Lalli, Frank (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 6)
    - 1985: Loeb, Marshall (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 7-8)
    - 1985: Maness, Dave (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 9)
    - 1985: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 10)
    - 1985: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 11)
    - 1985: Miller, Doug (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 12)
    - 1985: Munro, J. Richard (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 13)
    - 1985: Nicholas, Nicholas J. (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 14)
    - 1985: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 15)
    - 1985: Rogin, Gil (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 16)
    - 1985: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 17)
    - 1985: Ryan, Patricia (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 18)
    - 1985: Sheppe, P. Peter (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 19)
    - 1985: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 20)
    - 1985: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 21)
    - 1985: Taber, George (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 22)
    - 1985: Talbott, Strobe (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 23)
    - 1985: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 24)
    - 1985: Memos: A-E (Offsite-box 1015, Folder 25-30)
    - 1985: Memos: F-Z (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 1-19)
    - 1985: Memos: F-Z [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1985: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 20)
    - 1985: Memos to Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 21)
    - 1986: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 22)
    - 1986: Barnet, Bruce (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 23)
    - 1986: Brack, Reginald (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 24)
    - 1986: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 25)
    - 1986: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 26-28)
    - 1986: Daniels, Judy (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 29)
    - 1986: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 30)
    - 1986: Demaree, Allan (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 31)
    - 1986: Di Sapio, Rosemarie (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 32)
    - 1986: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 33)
    - 1986: Gardner, Marty (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 34)
    - 1986: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 35)
    - 1986: Guerette, Don: Long-Term Incentive Compensation Plan (Offsite-box 1016, Folder 36)
    - 1986: Guttman, William [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1986: Hiland, R. Bruce (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 1)
    - 1986: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 2)
    - 1986: Jones, Landon (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 3)
    - 1986: Kerr, Jeanne (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 4)
    - 1986: Kriss, Ron (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 5)
    - 1986: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 6)
    - 1986: Laffan, Doris: Stock Options (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 7)
    - 1986: Loeb, Marshall (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 8)
    - 1986: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 9)
    - 1986: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 10-12)
    - 1986: Muller, Henry (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 13)
    - 1986: Mulvoy, Mark (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 14)
    - 1986: Munro, J. Richard (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 15-16)
    - 1986: Nicholas, Nicholas J. (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 17)
    - 1986: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 18)
    - 1986: Rogin, Gil (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 19-20)
    - 1986: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 21)
    - 1986: Ryan, Patricia (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 22)
    - 1986: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 23)
    - 1986: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 24)
    - 1986: Talbott, Strobe (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 25)
    - 1986: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1017, Folder 26)
    - 1986: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 1)
    - 1986: Memos to Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 2)
    - 1986: Memos: A-W (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 3-24)
    - 1986: Memos: A-W [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Banks, Louis (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 25)
    - 1987: Barnet, Bruce (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 26)
    - 1987: Brack, Reginald (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 27)
    - 1987: Brack, Reginald [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Brine, Ruth (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 28)
    - 1987: Brine, Ruth [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Cave, Ray (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 29-30)
    - 1987: Constable, George [empty] (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 31)
    - 1987: Daniels, Judy (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 32)
    - 1987: Daniels, Judy [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Davidson, Ralph (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 33)
    - 1987: Demaree, Allan (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 34)
    - 1987: Di Sapio, Rosemarie (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 35)
    - 1987: Duncan, Dick (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 36)
    - 1987: Gardner, Marty (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 37)
    - 1987: Geisenheimer, Susan (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 38)
    - 1987: Geisenheimer, Susan [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Graves, Ralph (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 39)
    - 1987: Guerette, Don (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 40)
    - 1987: Guttman, William [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Hiland, R. Bruce [empty] (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 41)
    - 1987: Jamieson, Edward (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 42)
    - 1987: Jones, Landon (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 43)
    - 1987: Kerr, Jeanne [empty] (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 44)
    - 1987: Kriss, Ron (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 45)
    - 1987: Kunhardt, Phil (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 46)
    - 1987: Kunhardt, Phil [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Laffan, Doris (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 47)
    - 1987: Loeb, Marshall (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 48)
    - 1987: McCandless, Carolyn (Offsite-box 1018, Folder 49)
    - 1987: McManus, Jason (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 1-3)
    - 1987: Meigher, Christopher (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 4)
    - 1987: Miller, Bob (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 5)
    - 1987: Muller, Henry (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 6-7)
    - 1987: Mulvoy, Mark (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 8)
    - 1987: Munro, J. Richard (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 9)
    - 1987: Nicholas, Nicholas J. (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 10)
    - 1987: Prendergast, Curt (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 11)
    - 1987: Rogin, Gil (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 12)
    - 1987: Rogin, Gil [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Rukeyser, Bill (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 13)
    - 1987: Rukeyser, Bill [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Ryan, Patricia (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 14)
    - 1987: Ryan, Patricia [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
    - 1987: Stolley, Richard (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 15)
    - 1987: Sutton, Kelso (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 16)
    - 1987: Talbott, Strobe (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 17)
    - 1987: Wilson, Donald (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 18)
    - 1987: Memos to File (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 19)
    - 1987: Staff Memos (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 20)
    - 1987: Memos to Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 21)
    - 1987: Memos: Legal [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R18)
  - Subsubseries I.B.3. Departmental Files, 1946-1987; 25.0 Linear feet; (25 boxes)
    Topics of discussion include new features (What To Do About…, Sex Section); laws affecting the publishing/journalism field (Shield Law, Stanford Supreme Court decision); ideas for articles for special issues ("The Black Issue" and "Southern Issue"), and comment notes on Time Inc.'s magazines and their competitors such as Newsweek.
    Items of interest include includes remarks from several long-time employees on the history of Time including Roy Larsen in the 1973 Anniversary Dinner file; letters of congratulations in 1977 include one from President Jimmy Carter; a dummy for "Tempus," the Time College Supplement in the 1979 Magazine Development file; letters of congratulations in 1979 were received from the Librarian of Congress, National Security Advisor, Lee Iacocca, Rupert Murdoch, George Steinbrenner and Barbara Walters; a schedule of Vice President Mondale's 1979 visit to NYC and Time Inc.; handwritten, possible photocopy, letter from artist Andrew Wyeth in 1983; and a possible Entertainment Weekly precursor proposal in the 1984 Staff Magazine Ideas files.
    Early Files and 1963-1973 make up two groups of files found housed together, respectively, that are not from a single year. They were kept in the found groups, but reorganized chronologically. Some of the files designated as 1973 date from 1970 to 1972. 1974 has two sets of alphabetical files; one was transferred with a form and one was not, but is similar, though not duplicates, to the transferred set of files. The Departmental Files contain some name and memo files similar to Interoffice Correspondence that are not duplicates. Since these files were transferred to the Time Inc. Archives as Departmental Files, they have not been moved to Interoffice Correspondence.
    Organized chronologically by year, and retains original arrangement within each year.
    - Early Files: Henry Luce, 1946-1967 (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 22-23)
      This file is mainly about organizing Luce's obituary, articles regarding his death, and his Time cover. Includes research material on Luce in the form of two published speeches and his memos on the structure of the magazine.
    - Early Files: Whittaker Chambers, 1948-1959 (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 24)
      Includes Grunwald's letter to Chambers upon Chambers' resignation from Time Inc.
    - Early Files: Grunwald Memo on Time to T. S. Matthews, 1949 (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 25)
      Recounts Grunwald's concerns to managing editor Matthews including an intense dream.
    - Early Files: Miscellaneous Cover Stories, 1952 (Offsite-box 1019, Folder 26-27)
    - Early Files: U.S. Woman, 1952 (Offsite-box 1019-1020)
    - Early Files: Memo on Culture for Luce, 1953 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 2)
    - Early Files: Henry Luce: Memos to and from, 1953-1966 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 3-4)
    - Early Files: Grunwald Memo and Henry Luce: Foreign Policy, 1953-1966 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 5-6)
    - Early Files: Issue of Week Index, 1954 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 7)
    - Early Files: Research and Development, 1962 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 8)
    - Early Files: Utopia: Note and Drafts, 1962 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 9-10)
    - Early Files: Two Articles for Life: Unused, undated (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 11)
    - 1963: Time Fortieth Anniversary Dinner (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 12-13)
    - 1963-1973: Grunwald on Russia: Fortune, 1964 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 14)
    - 1963-1973: Vietnam: Essay Files, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 15-16)
    - 1963-1973: Assistant Managing Editor Congratulations, 1966 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 17)
    - 1963-1973: Marshall McLuhan, 1966 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 18)
    - 1963-1973: Cover Correspondence and Artists, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 1020, Folder 19-21)
    - 1963-1973: Behavior, 1968 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 1)
    - 1963-1973: Congratulations [Managing Editor appointment], 1968 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 2-5)
    - 1963-1973: Luce Memorial, 1968 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 6)
    - 1963-1973: Time Extra Supplement, 1968 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 7)
    - 1963-1973: Time, 1969 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 8a)
    - 1963-1973: Admitting Error About Vietnam, 1969 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 8b)
    - 1963-1973: Black [African Americans] Statistics / Black Issue, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 9-10)
    - 1963-1973: U.S. Mission: The American Century, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 11-12)
    - 1963-1973: U.S. Mission/American Century: Van Tassel Research, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 13)
    - 1963-1973: Newsweek: Fact from Opinion, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 14-15)
    - 1963-1973: Time Inc. Studies, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 16)
    - 1963-1973: Time Inc. Women, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 17-19)
      Contains materials on the 1971 sex discrimination case against Time Inc. and changes made to employment practices.
    - 1963-1973: Poll of Polls, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 20)
    - 1963-1973: Project Women, 1972 (Offsite-box 1021, Folder 21-22)
    - 1963-1973: Notes on "W" [Watergate] (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 1)
    - 1963-1973: For Time-Life Records: Music Album Intro?, undated (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 2)
    - 1972: New York University, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 3-4)
      Contains materials regarding Grunwald's participation on the School of Arts and Science President's Council.
    - 1973: Five-Year Plan (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 5)
    - 1973: Equality (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 6)
    - 1973: Women's Committee (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 7)
    - 1973: Court and the Press, Etc. (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 8)
    - 1973: What To Do About.... (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 9)
    - 1973: Supplements (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 10)
    - 1973: Irving Kristol (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 11)
    - 1973: Life (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 12)
    - 1973: Survey of Back of the Book (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 13)
    - 1973: Sex [Gender] Section (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 14)
    - 1973: Crossley Surveys, Inc. (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 15)
    - 1973: Shield Law (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 16)
    - 1973: Press: Future Speech Notes (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 17)
    - 1973: Congressional Meetings (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 18)
    - 1973: European Edition, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 19)
    - 1973: Time Anniversary Party (50th) (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 20-22)
    - 1973: Energy Conference (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 23)
    - 1974: Notes: Time (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 24-25)
    - 1974: Notes: Newsweek (Offsite-box 1022, Folder 26)